Summary

Focused and quick-learning Software Engineer with 2 years of experience. I am currently transitioning into full stack role (MEAN stack) from Java based framework experience.

Professional Skills

Java Core	Intermediate
MongoDB	Beginner
Node.js	Beginner
Express.js	Beginner
MySQL	Beginner
Javascript	Competent

Education

Jaypee Institute of Information Technology, Noida

B.Tech- CSE

Graduated July 2017

Rajhans Vidyalaya ,Mumbai

Plus Two

Graduated May 2013

Employment History

System engineer

Infosys Pvt. Ltd. Bengaluru, Karnataka July 2017 - Present

ONESOURCE- This project required the following skills: Core Java, Java struts, JS, Node.js,MySQL.lt was based on bank model and comprised of several modules ranging from rating the customer critical level to generating final reports regarding the customer including his loans, mortage etc. Also received appreciation mail for my work on few modules from the client.

Sep 2017- Apr 2019

SPECIALIST PROGRAMMER Role Change- I was selected for this programme in my current organisation. Consequently I was trained in MEAN stack recently and would be transitioning to full stack role. I had worked on a small training project where I handled both backend and frontend using MEAN technologies.

June 2019- present

https://www.linkedin.com/in/vibhorvaishprofile/

Hobbies & Interests

Contributing to competitive programming communities.

https://leetcode.com/vaishcr7/,

https://www.spoj.com/users/vaishcr7/

Watching football and learning about other cultures.